The weather forecast has been really off lately.
So much for only a 10% chance of rain.
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, good. You're not hurt?
That's not that much.
Please, don't come any closer to me.
Don't hurt me.
Please, please don't hurt me.
The rain comes from an unknown world, washing the Earth with its tears.
Is this new meeting a temporary necessity, or is it more likely to be a contrived coincidence?
Because, as we all know, there is more than one truth.
Don't hurt me.
, don't hurt me.
I choose to choose
Shino! I made these things called cookies!
We were supposed to make them during cooking class
and the other students taught me how!
So do you want to try one?
Sure. I'd love to. Thanks.
Hey, Tobichi.
No way! You get out!
Be careful, Shino! That witch is going to do more damage!
I'm so sorry.
Although I know an apology is hardly enough.
Why is this super genius apologizing to him?
What are we missing?
Maybe he's got some dirt on her.
That's so lame.
Oh, it's fine. You can stop bowing now.
Just don't worry about it, okay?
Listen up. No more cheating, okay?
Get your sticky hands off him!
The report said that you stayed.
Tell me what you're still doing here.
That's none of your business!
Now focus, Shino.
Forget about the stupid ugly witch and eat my cookies.
And mine.
I baked cookies too.
You need to stop copying me!
Actually, I baked mine first, so you're copying me.
Wrong!
And besides, look at your dumb cookies.
I bet they suck.
Come on.
Yeah, they're not all that great, so...
Here, eat! Quick before she tries to make you eat her junk!
No, you should try mine first.
Yum!
They're both good.
Mine must be better. He ate it much faster.
Incorrect. He ate mine .2 seconds faster than yours.
Excuse me?
Hey!
Some strange little stranger just gave me a whole bag of cookies.
Do you want one, Cheeto?
I'd let her, but she's watching her figure.
Man, it wasn't supposed to rain today, either.
Hmm.
Hey, Kotari, I made it home.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
Get out of here right now!
Kotari, what's going on?
Why is Toka here?
Hey!
Welcome back home, bro.
Oh, thanks.
Don't change the subject.
Now please tell me what Toka's doing in our house.
Well, I've decided she should live with us, you know, at least for the time being.
Okay, do you mind telling me why that is?
We have a good reason for this. Chill.
Reina?
What are you doing here?
Oh, sorry.
Am I using too much sugar again?
No.
Well, yes, but I don't really care about that.
Toka's aftercare.
That's right.
Fortunately, when she kissed you, her spirit power was immediately and effectively sealed.
And now, there is an invisible road.
What we call a path between the two of you.
Okay, but what's this thing about a seal?
I explained that to you after it happened.
When you kissed Toka after raising her mood points, you in particular were able to absorb her spirit powers and seal them.
So why is it I have that kind of power?
I'm not sure.
I just got lucky and figured it out.
With Ratataskar's help.
Can I continue with my point?
Now, if the spirit's mental condition becomes unstable, there is a significant probability that the power seals inside you will return back to her.
Huh?
Our research is conclusive. Toka's numbers are the most stable when she is near you.
Until the special housing unit for spirits is completed, it would be best for everyone if she stays here.
Right. Whatever.
This isn't a bad thing. Consider it a part of your training.
You mean I wasn't finished? Toka's powers are already sealed. What else am I supposed to do?
Did I say Toka was the only spirit around? There are more out there.
A lot more, in fact. Special designation disaster beings, also known as spirits.
They come in all shapes and sizes just like us.
We want you to continue speaking with them, Shin.
We need you to become even better at dealing with women.
The world needs you to become even better at dealing with women.
Great. No pressure at all. But I still don't get why I have to live with Toka.
I... I apologize, Shido. I knew it. I shouldn't be here.
No. You're fine. I'm a jerk.
This weird is never gonna end.
Shido! The light's out in the bathroom! Go change it immediately!
Of course. Fine. I'm on it.
Why does she have to be so mean when she's in her commander mode?
I'm normally the one to do this stuff, but still.
Sorry. I'm so sorry. I should have knocked.
Oh my god, you creep!
Someone was in a rush. Shame on Shido.
You did that on purpose.
I told you this was training, didn't I?
You need to learn how to face any situation calm and collected.
Toka! I'm sorry. I didn't know you were in there.
It's fine. I forgive you.
Just... hand that to me, please.
Shido, I got a bath all ready for you. You can go ahead and wash up.
Nah, I'm good. You go instead.
Oh, and here. You can use these if you want.
Kotari has never given up first dibs when I've got these.
She should know not to underestimate me.
I, Shidoitsuka, haven't grown up in the same house as you without learning a thing or two.
That's so nice.
But, uh, why don't you go ahead and use them?
I think so.
Hey, Toka. You're not taking a bath right now?
No. I'm standing in this door.
Maybe I was being too suspicious.
Go figure, there are spirits besides Toka.
I wonder how many there are.
And will I be able to save them all?
Kotari, I'm gonna kill you!
Not my fault, you're dumb.
Oh, crap!
Charge!
Hm?
Whoa!
Um, hi.
You can't just bump out at me like that, you know?
And another fail.
This is supposed to be my training.
Shido!
It's time for lunch!
Why are you here, witch?
You're not welcome.
I was going to say the same thing.
Can't we all just eat together?
What?
What is it?
Share all you want, I'm not sharing.
Excuse me, what is that?
Uh, the thing is, this morning we bought our bentos from the same place.
I bumped into Toka while she was there.
Liar!
You bought this 154 days ago at the discount store in front of the station for $15.80.
You've been using the same container ever since.
This is not from the bento shop.
And how exactly do you know this?
That's not really important.
Ugh!
Don't leave me out of the conversation like that, it's rude!
Now what are you two talking about?
Hey!
Cheeto!
My girlfriend wants me to help her pick out clothes.
Do you think a French maid is best?
Shrine maiden? Nurse?
Maybe stripper?
Dude, this is not the best time!
Who cares if she's a maid or whatever else?
Maid it is!
Thanks, man!
Your attention, please.
This is not a drill.
There have been precursory signs of an imminent spatial quake in this vicinity.
We evacuate to the nearest shelter immediately.
I repeat, there have been precursory signs of an imminent spatial...
Kids! Another quake alarm!
We have to evacuate immediately!
Move it or lose it, as they say!
Lee?
Yeah.
You want me to leave her behind?
Yes.
Remember, her powers have been sealed, so she's the same as a normal human being.
Besides, we can't afford for her stress levels to go up.
Watching a fight might trigger that.
That's true.
Shito! Toka! Miss Murasame!
Why are you dawdling back there?
If you don't hurry up and evacuate, you're gonna be in serious trouble and serious danger!
Miss Okamine, will you watch Toka for me?
What? Of course!
I'll keep an eye on her.
Shito...
Hey, Toka.
I need to leave you here, okay?
Something just came up.
I have to go, but I'll be right back.
Now? It's dangerous.
I'll be fine, I promise!
Shito Itaka, come back here!
You too, Miss Murasame!
Where do you think you're going?
Oh, Shito...
Hey, you made it.
Well, for the aftermath anyway.
It's smaller than usual this time.
I'd like to say this was a good sign, but this is about average for a hermit.
Hermit?
The name of the spirit that's appeared this time.
She's known for being more docile than the other spirits we've seen.
Hold on. I've seen this girl before.
Where and when?
I met her at the shrine. Two nights ago.
We were already tracking her by then, but we saw no disruption of her main spirit wave numbers at that time.
So, it's the same as it was for Toka.
The AST has arrived. They are commencing their attack.
How can they fire on a little girl?
What she looks like doesn't matter to the AST.
She's trying to run away. What they're doing is wrong.
Don't feel sorry for her, Shito.
That behavior will only make you weak.
Kotari!
Let's do it.
I want to go save that girl.
There you go. That's so my big brother for you.
Listen up! Prepare for a Type 1 capture!
Right!
Okay. I think it's about time we go on another date.
Hermit has entered the building.
AST, I want you to hold your positions until the target is moved.
So, you think Hermit is really going to come here?
Yes. Based on the analysis, there's no doubt.
The AST probably won't be able to make a move for a while.
Don't tell me you're here to bully Yoshinan too!
Oh? The Lucky Letcher has returned for more, hasn't he?
Shito, hold on a sec.
Talk to me, people. Name your choice.
Come on! It's gotta be two!
This one's straight out of a dating sim. Go with two!
Isn't that risky if you don't know the other person's personality?
Seems one is our best bet.
Hermit rarely attacks humans.
I'm gonna have to go with option three.
Shito, go with three!
Uh, are you sure about that?
Come on. Don't you know someone who would talk like that?
Tonomachi.
Excuse me. I don't know what you mean. I'm just a wandering vagabond.
You're trying to make me laugh, aren't you? Nobody talks like that seriously.
Well, I'm glad you liked my joke.
So, my name's Shito. You are?
Oh, I'm sorry! How embarrassing! I can't believe I forgot to introduce myself to you!
My name is Yoshinan!
Isn't it cute? Isn't it cute?
Uh, yeah. Sure, it's cute.
So, is that your name? Or is it the name of the puppet?
Do you guys share a name?
Shito! Her happiness meter just went down dramatically!
What did you say to her?
What? Nothing, I swear. I was just trying to find out why she only talks through ventriloquism.
I do not know what you were talking about, Shito. What is ventriloquism?
Look, we'll figure out the cause of this later. For now, just work on making her happy again.
Right, yeah, I get your point. So Yoshinan's just Yoshinan.
Oh, Shito! You're one of those people who jokes around a lot, aren't you? Why did you come here?
Oh, because... Well, I know it's sudden. But will... Will you go on a date with me?
A date?
Do you think it's really all that dangerous outside?
There's no telling how dangerous it is! But with a spatial quake, it's not worth the risk!
Seriously?
Toka doesn't know about spatial quakes?
Maybe she's like a spoiled, super rich girl.
That's so lame!
Ms. Okamine, why do you think Shito would leave during such a dangerous time?
Honestly, I have no idea.
You don't?
She wants to save him. She's totally brave.
I want to be here when I grow up.
That's so lame?
Well, I'm sure Shito will be perfectly fine. There's really nothing to worry about, Toka. You'll see.
Huh?
Permission to shoot?
Not gonna happen for a while.
We're talking about a weak little hermit here. She hasn't been that much of a threat yet.
Nothing worth city damage and a call for support troops.
The conditions with her are different than those with Princess.
I still can't get over it.
A girl looking just like Princess transfers into your class without any spirit reactions detected.
There's seemingly nothing wrong with her family register either.
I keep racking my brain trying to figure it out.
But to tell you the truth, I got nothing.
Tell me what you think! Am I cool or am I the coolest ever?
Hey, wait, that's not safe!
Hey, wait! I asked if I was cool or the coolest!
That... that was, uh... I, uh, didn't mean...
Crap, she's gonna be pissed.
Ow!
Sorry about that, Shito. I wasn't paying enough attention.
Shito, it's an emergency!
What? Emergency?
Toka?
Shito, what were you doing just then?
What do you mean?
So after you worried me half to death, you came here to make out with her?
How dare you!
See what I mean? You're looking at a rather unstable mental condition.
Her spirit powers are gradually flowing back into her.
Really? What should I do?
How rude! Why didn't you tell me the something that came up was meeting this weird looking little girl?
Uh, no, uh, she's, uh...
Hello there, angry lady!
My name's Toka.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news, Toka, but it seems as though Shito's gotten bored with you!
Based on what you've already communicated, Shito stood you up to come here and hang out with me instead, isn't that right?
I think that's fairly conclusive.
No! What are you talking about?
Shito, you shut your mouth right now!
I do apologize, though. Being second best is never an easy thing, is it?
It's because I'm so charming, not because there's anything wrong with you, Toka.
But it's not like you can blame Shito for blowing you off so he can come play with me.
I am pretty adorable.
No! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! This can't be happening! Look at me!
You can scream all you want! But you're about to hear the brutal truth!
Go on, Shito, tell this poor thing she's not wanted anymore!
I am too wanted! You... you don't know!
Shito is the one who said it was okay for me to stay here with him!
Why are you lying to me and being so mean? I won't take it anymore!
Say something! Come on, why aren't you talking now? Speak!
What's wrong? It won't talk! Make it talk!
I was trying to talk. Give it back. Please!
What are you doing in there?
The hermit's mental condition is all over the place, too. They need to calm down.
Hey, so listen, Toka. Could you maybe give that back to her, maybe?
Shito, she was right. You really do like her better than me.
No, it's not that at all!
Got you!
Uh, what's that?
What's that?
Oh, no! She's releasing her angel!
This is bad! You have to get out of there now!
Her angel?
Did you forget Toka's sandal bun?
Watch out!
Maybe, maybe, her soul!
Oh, no, she's getting close!
The next living house нажその敷き, she lives in real间.
Oh, no, she doesn't presentation!
It may be a battle!
Take her!
We got 3X-6.
We lost her.
Everyone, return to base.
You okay, Toka? You're not hurt?
I'm all right. Will you just get away?
But why?
Don't touch me!
You like that little girl better than me. I know you do. Admit it!
Wait, what?
That's perfect. Looks like someone's got trouble in paradise.
I don't have time for dollop.
On the ground.
Watch this video.
Not at all.
There is another way to engage the word
they take their creatures
Which one is again
A разр space
to get the drive I live to for the time
And out of luck
The速 langer can begin with the Hit
Will you meet me again? Will you believe me again?
Will you be looking for love?
Take the world!
The world will end before living in the world
If you are laughing, I'll be happy
Good, how much?
To be continued...